{
    "subject": "resource/People's_Socialist_Republic_of_Albania",
    "predicate": "ontology/currency",
    "object": "resource/Albanian_lek",
    "human_readable": "The currency of the People's Socialist Republic of Albania is Albanian lek.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.8557916879653931,
            "question": "What is the currency of Albania?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7276121377944946,
            "question": "Is the Albanian lek a strong or weak currency compared to others?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7037835121154785,
            "question": "What is the name of the Albanian lek?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.676133930683136,
            "question": "What type of republic is Albania?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6708160638809204,
            "question": "In what country is the Albanian lek used?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5844470262527466,
            "question": "What are some common uses for the Albanian lek?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5323887467384338,
            "question": "How is the Albanian lek regulated by the government?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5060269236564636,
            "question": "What factors influence the value of the Albanian lek?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.33443260192871094,
            "question": "Are there any historical events that have impacted the Albanian lek?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.2995348870754242,
            "question": "How does the Albanian lek exchange rate fluctuate?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=The currency of the People's Socialist Republic of Albania is Albanian lek.",
            "html": "dbpedia_9248_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Are there any historical events that have impacted the Albanian lek?",
            "html": "dbpedia_9248_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What factors influence the value of the Albanian lek?",
            "html": "dbpedia_9248_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=How is the Albanian lek regulated by the government?",
            "html": "dbpedia_9248_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_9248_23.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_9248_24.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_9248_30.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_9248_4.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_9248_5.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_9248_57.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_9248_58.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_9248_60.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_9248_68.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_9248_8.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "After evaluating the documents, I can confirm that:\n\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}"
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```\n\nThe provided documents contain information about the Albanian Lek, confirming that it is indeed the currency of Albania. Therefore, the statement \"The currency of the People's Socialist Republic of Albania is Albanian lek\" is supported by the given context."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "The Most Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}